https://my.boatingsafety.com/page/privacy

Privacy Policy - Sea Tow Foundation
Contact Us | Print Page | Report Abuse | Sign In | Register
Toggle navigationMENUHomeDonateHelp Get InvolvedGet Our NewsletterConnect with Boating Safety GroupsLearn About Sea Tow FoundationPrograms Life Jacket Loaner ProgramFlare Disposal ProgramSober Skipper Program Advisory CouncilResourcesBlogShop
Edit This Favorite
Name:
Category:
Share:
Yes
No, Keep Private
Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy Sea Tow Foundation is committed to respecting and protecting your privacy. This privacy policy covers important aspects of how we respect and protect your privacy, including: Awareness, Information Gathered, Use of Information, Third-party Use, Choice, Accuracy & Access, Security and Enforcement. Awareness Sea Tow Foundation provides this Privacy Policy to make you aware of our practices and of the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and from the bottom of every web page of our sites. Information Gathered On our website, you can do some or all of the following:  become a member of our boating safety community at no charge, renew your membership at no charge, manage your account, subscribe to our newsletter, order products, download printable products, chat with us, email us and request information. The types of personal information collected at these pages may include your name, address, contact and billing information, transaction and credit card information and information. Additionally, any information you supply due to promotional programs, refer a friend programs or special offers may be collected. In order to continuously improve our products and services, we may also ask you to provide us with information regarding your personal or professional interests, demographics, experience with our programs and products, and more detailed contact preferences. When you access our website, we may automatically collect information that is not personally-identifiable including, but not limited to, the type of browser or device and computer operating system you use; the domain name of the website from which you came; the device ID number, the number of visits, average time spent and pages viewed. We may use this information and share it with our worldwide affiliates to measure the use of our websites and mobile app and improve their content. Use of Information Sea Tow Foundation uses your information to better understand your needs and to provide you with better service. Specifically, we use your information to help you complete transactions, to communicate with you, to update you on services and benefits and to personalize our website and mobile app for you. Credit card numbers are used only for payment processing and are not retained for other purposes. We may also use your information to periodically contact you for market research or to provide you with marketing information we think would be of particular interest to you. At a minimum, we will always give you the opportunity to opt-out of receiving such direct marketing or market research contact. Third-party Use Sea Tow Foundation will not sell, rent or lease your personally identifiable information to others. Unless we have your permission or are required by law, we will only share the personal data you provide online with other Sea Tow entities and/or business partners who are acting on our behalf for the uses described above. Such Sea Tow entities and/or business partners are governed by our privacy policies with respect to the use of this data and are bound by appropriate confidentiality agreements. Choice Sea Tow Foundation will not use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without first letting you know and offering you a choice. We will also provide you the opportunity to let us know if you do not wish to receive unsolicited direct marketing materials from us and we will do everything we can to honor such requests. Your permission is always secured first, should we ever share your information with third parties that are not acting on our behalf and governed by our privacy policy. Accuracy & Access Upon request, Sea Tow Foundation will provide a summary of any personal information retained by Sea Tow Foundation. You may modify, correct, change or update your personal information or cause it to be removed from Sea Tow Foundation's database. We try to ensure that any information we collect and maintain is reliable and current. Individuals who desire additional information on the accuracy of and access to their personally identifiable information should contact Sea Tow Foundation’s Compliance Officer at: Compliance Officer Sea Tow Foundation, Inc. P.O. Box 1325 Southold, NY 11971 USA info@boatingsafety.com
Any links to third party web sites are provided solely as a convenience to you. If you use these links, you will leave our site. Sea Tow Foundation has not reviewed all of these third-party sites and does not control and is not responsible for any of these sites, their content or their privacy policy. Thus, Sea Tow Foundation does not endorse or make any representations about them, or any information, services, products or other materials found there, or any results that may be obtained from using them. Security Sea Tow Foundation is committed to ensuring the security of your information. To prevent unauthorized access or disclosure, maintain data accuracy and to ensure the appropriate use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online and through our mobile app. For example, we use encryption when collecting or transferring sensitive data such as credit card information. We cannot guarantee the confidentiality of any communication or material transmitted to/from Sea Tow Foundation via this site or mobile website, however. For more private communication, you may contact us by telephone at 888-276-7691. Any inquiries concerning security should be reported to Sea Tow Foundation’s Compliance Officer. Contact information is provided above.
Enforcement Individuals who wish to file a complaint or who take issue with Sea Tow Foundation’s Privacy Policy should direct such communication to Sea Tow Foundation’s Compliance Officer at the address above. Sea Tow Foundation’s Compliance Officer will explain the process to be followed when filing a complaint. Sea Tow Foundation, Inc. is subject to the jurisdiction of the U.S. Federal Trade Commission. Should an individual be unable to resolve a complaint by contacting Sea Tow Foundation’s Compliance Officer, they may contact the Federal Trade Commission at the following address: Federal Trade Commission Attn: Consumer Response center 600 Pennsylvania Avenue NW Washington, DC 20580 consumerline@ftc.gov www.ftc.gov
Information Placed Automatically on Your Computer When you view our website, we may store some information on your computer or mobile device in the form of a "cookie" to automatically recognize you the next time you visit. Cookies can help us in many ways, for example, by allowing us to tailor a website to better match your interests or to save your password so that you do not have to re-enter it each time. If you choose not to be recognized, please refer to your Internet browser to erase cookies from your computer hard drive, block all cookies or receive a warning before a cookie is stored.
Children No personal information should be submitted to Sea Tow Foundation's website by children without the consent of their parent or guardian. Sea Tow Foundation encourages all parents or guardians to instruct their children in the safe and responsible use of their Personal Information while using the Internet. Sea Tow Foundation will not knowingly collect or use any Personal Information collected from children for any purpose whatsoever, including disclosure to third parties. Policy Changes The foregoing policy is presently in effect. Sea Tow Foundation reserves the right to change this policy at any time and we will post such changes. By entering the Sea Tow Foundation website, you are accepting all terms and conditions outlined in the above Privacy Policy.
With a focus on safe boating practices that result in fun on the water, the Sea Tow Foundation – a 501(c)(3) nonprofit organization – was established in 2007 by Sea Tow Founder Capt. Joe Frohnhoefer. After his passing in 2015, Captain Joe’s legacy continues as the Foundation brings attention to the number of preventable boating-related injuries, deaths, and damage to property, that directly addresses prevention methods through education and awareness. For more information contact us at: Email: info@boatingsafety.com Phone: (888) 276-7691
Latest News
more
9/24/2020Sea Tow Foundation DIY Craft Time: Nautical Picture Frame9/2/2020Sea Tow Foundation Announces Official Call for Entry
for National Boating Industry Safety Awards
Calendar
more
The upcoming calendar is currently empty.Click here to view past events and photos »
Newest Members
E. SonstebyBoating Safety: Freedom Boat ClubB. RosellaBoating Safety: Freedom Boat ClubB. ParkerBoating Safety: Freedom Boat ClubA. SutterBoating Safety: Freedom Boat ClubC. SpeckmanBoating Safety: Freedom Boat ClubA. RevakBoating Safety: Freedom Boat ClubC. MullenBoating Safety: Freedom Boat ClubD. CantrellBoating Safety: Freedom Boat ClubB. ParkerBoating Safety: Freedom Boat ClubC. KellyBoating Safety: Freedom Boat ClubD. LundBoating Safety: Freedom Boat ClubA. SpaethBoating Safety: Freedom Boat ClubB. SprengBoating Safety: Freedom Boat ClubA. GossBoating Safety: Freedom Boat ClubK. VollbrechtBoating Safety: Freedom Boat ClubB. MarquardtBoating Safety: Freedom Boat ClubA. HardBoating Safety: Freedom Boat ClubD. HasbrouckBoating Safety: Freedom Boat ClubM. CarrickBoating Safety: Freedom Boat ClubM. O'HaraBoating Safety: Freedom Boat ClubJ. SprengBoating Safety: Freedom Boat ClubR. DobreffBoating Safety: Freedom Boat ClubL. GoldbergBoating Safety: Freedom Boat ClubL. BowieBoating Safety: Freedom Boat ClubR. AtkinsonBoating Safety: Freedom Boat ClubS. IssacksBoating Safety: Freedom Boat ClubK. SeeligBoating Safety: Freedom Boat ClubJ. WeirBoating Safety: Freedom Boat ClubT. RosellaBoating Safety: Freedom Boat ClubM. HillsBoating Safety: Freedom Boat Club
Online Surveys
Sea Tow Foundation:
Sober Skipper:
Sea Tow Foundation - P.O. Box 1325 - Southold, NY 11971www.boatingsafety.com - 888-276-7691 – All Rights Reserved © 2020Privacy Policy - Terms
Membership Software Powered by YourMembership  ::  Legal
